Guide to the Trustees of Lingnan University Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Consolidated General File, 1926-1977; Series I
  - Methodist Missionary Society (London), 1952 (Box 17, Folder 236)
  - Miscellaneous Staff Correspondence: Baker-Holt, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 237)
  - Miscellaneous Staff Correspondence: House-Woods, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 238)
  - Montgomery, Ethel, 1935-1952 (Box 17, Folder 239)
  - Moonitz, Maurice, 1964,1967 (Box 17, Folder 240)
  - N (Box 18, Folder 241)
  - National City Bank, 1950-1954 (Box 18, Folder 242-243)
  - New York Alumni Association Lists of Alumni, 1952-1953 (Box 18, Folder 244)
  - New York, State of: Amendments and Registration, 1964-1970 (Box 18, Folder 245)
  - New York, State of: Department of Social Welfare, 1954-1963 (Box 18, Folder 246)
  - New York, State of: Department of Labor, 1960-1967 (Box 18, Folder 247)
  - New York, State of: Income Taxes, 1963-1964 (Box 18, Folder 248)
  - New York, State of: Office of Attorney General, Charitable Foundation Division, 1967 (Box 18, Folder 249)
  - New York, University of the State of, 1931-1965 (Box 18, Folder 250-251)
  - New York Trust Company, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 252)
  - O (Box 18, Folder 253)
  - Pa-Pla (Box 18, Folder 254)
  - Pli-Pu (Box 18, Folder 255)
  - Paddock, Louise S. (Estate of), 1956 (Box 18, Folder 256)
  - Parker, Philo W., 1952-1970 (Box 18, Folder 257)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1955-1958 (Box 18, Folder 258)
  - Pension Matters, 1944-1982 (Box 19, Folder 259-266)
  - Plimpton, Francis T.P. (See also: Debevoise, Plimpton and McLean), 1952-1965 (Box 19, Folder 267)
  - Pope, Frederick, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 268)
  - Pott, James H., 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 269)
  - Pride, Richard E., 1952-1957 (Box 19, Folder 270)
  - Q-Ra (Box 19, Folder 271)
  - Re (Box 19, Folder 272)
  - Ri-Ru (Box 19, Folder 273)
  - Radio Corporation of Amerlca, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 274)
  - Rahill, William A., 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 275)
  - Rhoads, Howard G., 1936,1951-1953 (Box 20, Folder 276)
  - Riley, William A., 1952-1961 (Box 20, Folder 277)
  - Robinson, James H., 1953 (Box 20, Folder 278)
  - Sa-Si (Box 20, Folder 279)
  - Sk-Sp (Box 20, Folder 280)
  - St-Sz (Box 20, Folder 281)
  - Science Journal, 1952-1953 (Box 20, Folder 282)
  - Science Journal: Index; Vols. 13-16, Nos. 1-4; Vol. 17, No. 1, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 283)
  - Seaman, H.B., 1953 (Box 20, Folder 284)
  - Seaman's Bank for Savings, 1948-1957 (Box 20, Folder 285)
  - Seymour, Lawrence D., 1952-1977 (Box 20, Folder 286)
  - Shiu, Kai Mui, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 287)
  - Siu, Tso-Fai, 1947 (Box 20, Folder 288)
  - Smithsonian Institution, 1954-1956 (Box 20, Folder 289)
  - Southern Passenger Association Clergy Bureau, 1952-1957 (Box 20, Folder 290)
  - Special Funds, 1936,1963 (Box 20, Folder 291)
  - Spivey, Nellie I., 1954-1957 (Box 20, Folder 292)
  - Staff: Directory of Foreign Staff of Lingnan University (1898-1951), 1952 (Box 20, Folder 293)
  - Streeter, Edward, 1952-1957 (Box 20, Folder 294)
  - Szeto, Yau S., 1952 (Box 20, Folder 295)
  - Sz-To, Wai, 1952-1955 (Box 20, Folder 296)
  - Szutu, Chan (Gene), 1952-1973 (Box 20, Folder 297)
  - Ta-Ton (Box 21, Folder 298)
  - Tor-Tz (Box 21, Folder 299)
  - Tong, Fuk-Cheung: Fund, 1944-1966 (Box 21, Folder 300-301)
  - Trustees: communications, 1952-1979 (Box 21, Folder 301A-305)
  - Trustees: Personnel, 1945-1969 (Box 21, Folder 306-307)
  - Treasury Department: Bureau of Customs, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 308)
  - Tsang, Yin Sang, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 309)
  - U-V (Box 22, Folder 310)
  - United Board for Christian Colleges in China (See also: Fenn, William P.), 1945-1953 (Box 22, Folder 310A-311)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1955-1980 (Box 22, Folder 312-313)
  - United States Department of Commerce, 1947-1952 (Box 22, Folder 313A)
  - United States Treasury Department Foreign Assets Control, 1951 (Box 22, Folder 314)
  - Wa-Wic (Box 22, Folder 315)
  - Wil-Wz (Box 22, Folder 316)
  - Walline, E.E., 1953 (Box 22, Folder 317)
  - Wang, Shih-Chao, 1954-1955 (Box 22, Folder 318)
  - Wannamaker, Olin D., 1932-1942 (Box 22, Folder 319-329)
  - Wannamaker, Olin D., 1943-1970 (Box 23, Folder 330-344)
  - Wei, Henry, 1953-1954 (Box 23, Folder 345)
  - Western Clergy Bureau, 1952,1961 (Box 23, Folder 346)
  - White, Gilbert F., 1952-1958 (Box 23, Folder 347)
  - White, Lester and Company (Accountants), 1969-1980 (Box 23, Folder 348-351)
  - Wilbur, Brayton, 1952 (Box 24, Folder 352)
  - Williams-in-Asia, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 353-355)
  - Wisner Memorial Fund, O.F. Wisner, Francis P., 1953-1954 (Box 24, Folder 356)
  - Wong, Wing-Tze, 1953 (Box 24, Folder 357)
  - Woods, Andrew H., 1956 (Box 24, Folder 358)
  - Yale-in-China, 1959-1980 (Box 24, Folder 359-366)
  - Yu, Chau-Shing, 1951-1956 (Box 24, Folder 367)
  - Yung, Ying-Chi, 1953-1954 (Box 24, Folder 368)
  - X-Y-Z (Box 24, Folder 369)
- Administrative Records, 1945-1982,n.d.; Series II
  Following two folders related to legal documents and the disposition of the Lingnan archives, material related to the annual and semi-annual meetings of the Trustees, is chronologically arranged. This material includes agendas, minutes and supporting documents. Following the meeting-related materials are records from committees of the Board of Trustees, alphabetically arranged by the name of the committee.
  - Constitution and By-Laws, 1949-1962,n.d. (Box 25, Folder 370)
  - Disposition of Archives, 1954-1977 (Box 25, Folder 371)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1946 (Box 25, Folder 372)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1952 (Box 25, Folder 373)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1953 (Box 25, Folder 374)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1954 (Box 25, Folder 375)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1955 (Box 25, Folder 376)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1956 (Box 25, Folder 377)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1957 (Box 25, Folder 378)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 379)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1959 (Box 25, Folder 380)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1960 (Box 26, Folder 381)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 386-387)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 388-389)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1967 Dec 5 (Box 27, Folder 391)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1968 (Box 27, Folder 392-393)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 394-396)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 397-398)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1971 Jun 8 (Box 27, Folder 399)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1971 Dec 7 (Box 28, Folder 400)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1972 (Box 28, Folder 401-402)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 403-404)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 405)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 406-407)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 408-409)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1977 (Box 28, Folder 410-411)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 412-413)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1979 (Box 29, Folder 414-415)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 416-417)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 418-419)
  - Annual and Semi-Annual Meetings of the Board of Trustees, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 420)
  - Indices to Minutes of Meetings, 1957-1964 (Box 30, Folder 421)
  - Form Letters: re. Votes of Trustees, 1953-1959 (Box 30, Folder 422-423)
  - Miscellaneous Circulation Votes, 1954-1955 (Box 30, Folder 424)
  - Miscellaneous Proxies, 1955-1970 (Box 30, Folder 425-429)
  - Directors' Meetings (including meeting on of Canton Union Theological College) Committees, 1945-1948 1947 Jan 14 (Box 39, Folder 446)
  - Executive Committee, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 447)
  - Finance Committee, 1948-1971 (Box 39, Folder 448-459)
  - Nominating Committee and Board Membership, 1952-1969 (Box 39, Folder 460-462)
  - Policy Committee, 1959 (Box 39, Folder 463)
  - Program Planning Committee Long Range Study Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 39, Folder 464-466)
  - Re-Establishment Committee, 1956-1959 (Box 39, Folder 467-468)
  - Special Trustees Committee: Appropriations, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 468A)
- Financial Records, 1919-1981; Series III
  No effort has been made to distinguish between the various financial ledgers in this series. Inclusive dates are provided. The miscellaneous financial documents of Box 37 remain in the safe box as they arrived. Two documents were removed from this box; the agreements between the Lingnan Trustees and the Chinese University of Hong Kong have been placed with similar material in the Consolidated General File (Box 1, Folder 5). Additional investment review records are also available in Series I, filed under "Bank of New York".
  - Financial Ledgers, 1919-1928 (Box 31, Folder 430)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1929-1936 (Box 32, Folder 432)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1924-1926 (Box 33, Folder 434)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1929-1940 (Box 34, Folder 435)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1932-1963 (Box 35, Folder 436)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1951 (Box 36, Folder 437)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1926-1941 (Box OV1)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1940-1941 (Box OV2)
  - Financial Ledgers, 1940-1962 (Box OV3)
  - Miscellaneous Financial Documents, 1943-1970 (Box 37, Folder 439)
  - Investment Review Records, 1971-1981 (Box 38, Folder 440-441)
  - Trial Balance Sheets, 1953-1966 (Box 38, Folder 442-445)
- Related Institutions and Programs, 1954-1981; Series IV
  The institutions and programs are listed alphabetically. Sub-divisions within these categories exist in some cases. In other cases, the material has been left in basic chronological order.
  - Chinese University of Hong Kong
    - Building Program, Architect's Renderings, Correspondence, 1967 (Box 40, Folder 469)
    - Publications Bulletin, 1966-1980 (Box 40, Folder 470)
    - Publications: Development Plan, 1964 (Box 40, Folder 471)
    - Publications: Vice Chancellor's Reports, 1963-1974 (Box 40, Folder 472)
    - Social Research Center, 1973-1980 (Box 40, Folder 473-474)
    - Social Research Center: Reports, 1977-1979 (Box 40, Folder 475)
  - Chung Chi College
    - Correspondence: Allen, Yorke Jr. (See also: Series I), 1954-1966 (Box 41, Folder 476-479)
    - Correspondence: Appeal Letters, 1954-1961 (Box 41, Folder 480)
    - Correspondence: Lee, Y.L., 1952-1954 (Box 41, Folder 481)
    - Correspondence: Lin, Dao-Yang, 1957-1960 (Box 41, Folder 482)
    - Correspondence: Yung, C.T., 1961-1968 (Box 41, Folder 483-484)
    - Financial Records: Budget, 1959-1960 (Box 41, Folder 485)
    - Publications: Brochures, 1958,1959 (Box 41, Folder 486)
    - Publications: Bulletins, 1955-1967 (Box 41, Folder 487-488)
    - Publications: Calendar, 1965-1966 1967-1968 (Box 42, Folder 489)
    - Publications: Chinese Literary Review (in Chinese), c. 1957 (Box 42, Folder 490)
    - Publications: Chung Chi College Story in Pictures, 1957 (Box 42, Folder 491)
    - Publications: The Chung Chi Journal, 1963 (Box 42, Folder 492)
    - Publications: Class Book, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 493)
    - Publications: Special Bulletin, 1955 (Box 42, Folder 494)
    - Report of Y.K. Chu to the Trustees re. Trip to Hong Kong, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 495)
    - Committee on Scholarly Communication with the People's Republic of China, 1974-1977 (Box 42, Folder 496)
  - Hong Kong Baptist College
    - Correspondence, 1967-1976 (Box 42, Folder 497)
    - Published Reports, 1973-1978 (Box 42, Folder 498)
  - Lingnan College
    - Various, including correspondence re. Sui Ming Lee, University of Pittsburgh Grant, 1967-1972 (Box 43, Folder 499-505)
    - Various, 1973-1980 (Box 44, Folder 506-513)
    - Publications: Lingnan Newsletter, 1974,1975 (Box 44, Folder 514)
    - Lingnan College Prospectus, 1972-1974, 1974-1977, 1977-1979 (Box 44)
    - Lingnan Education Organization Limited, 1969,1973 (Box 45, Folder 515)
    - Lingnan Fellowship Program for Faculty Development Lingnan Institute of Business Administration, 1974-1980 (Box 45, Folder 516-518)
    - Various, 1963-1964 (Box 45, Folder 519-523)
    - Various, 1965-1967 (Box 46, Folder 524-532)
    - Various, 1968-1971 (Box 47, Folder 533-539)
    - Various, 1972-1977 (Box 48, Folder 540-552)
    - Various, 1978-1908 (Box 49, Folder 553-556)
    - Publications: Graduate Programmes, 1971-1981 (Box 49, Folder 558-559)
    - Publications: Fulton Commission Report, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 560)
    - Publications: Bulletin, 1969, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 561)
    - Publications: AMP-Series, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 561)
    - Publications: MBA News, 1980 (Box 49, Folder 561)
    - Publications IESE Catalogue, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 561)
    - Publications: Programme of Studies Course Description, n.d. (Box 49, Folder 561)
  - Lingnan Middle School
    - Various, 1955-1968 (Box 50, Folder 562-565)
    - Financial Records, 1957-1965 (Box 50, Folder 565)
    - Publications, 1960-1966, n.d. (Box 50, Folder 566)
  - Midwest Chinese Student and Alumni Services
    - Newsletter, 1965 (Box 50, Folder 567)
  - National Committee U.S./China Relations
    - Correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box 50, Folder 568)
    - Publications: Newsletters, Annual Reports, Brochures, 1973-1979 (Box 50, Folder 569)
  - New Asia Research Institute
    - Various, 1957-1960 (Box 50, Folder 570)
  - University of Pittsburgh
    - Sociology Proposal: Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 50, Folder 571-572)
- Photographs, 1898-1973; Series V
  The photographs are listed alphabetically by subject matter within the following categories:
  1. Buildings and Scenes
  a. College Buildings and Grounds
  b. South China Scenes
  2. Campus Life
  3. Individual and Group Portraits
  a. Faculty
  b. Students
  c. Trustees and Directors
  d. Benefactors and Donors
  e. Visitors
  f. Miscellaneous
  - Buildings and Scenes
    - College Buildings and Grounds
      - Aerial Views, Plans, Models, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 573)
      - Agriculture, Engineering, 1930,1933,1956 (Box 51, Folder 574)
      - Agriculture: College Cannery, 1921 (Box 51, Folder 575)
      - Atwood Laboratory Science Hall (Willard Straight Building) Freeman Meteorological Station, 1926-1928,1933 (Box 51, Folder 576)
      - Dormitories: Wing Kwong Hall Women's Dormitories, 1924-1935 (Box 51, Folder 577)
      - Dormitories: Middle School Overseas Dormitory Java Hall Miscellaneous, 1912-1973 (Box 51, Folder 578)
      - Foods and Clothing Laboratories, 1931 (Box 51, Folder 579)
      - Grant Hall, 1929 (Box 51, Folder 580)
      - Infirmary, n.d. (Box 51, Folder 581)
      - Martin Hall, 1908-1932 (Box 51, Folder 582)
      - Matsheds (Residences), 1922 (Box 52, Folder 583)
      - Medical Buildings, 1918-1931 (Box 52, Folder 584)
      - Middle School Dining Hall Recitation Hall, 1930-1936 (Box 52, Folder 585)
      - Miscellaneous Girls' School, 1919,1932 (Box 52, Folder 586)
      - Model Village Houses for Junior Members of Staff, 1924,1926,1932 (Box 52, Folder 587)
      - Panoramas, 1913,1927-1931 (Box 52, Folder 588)
      - Primary School Buildings, 1930 (Box 52, Folder 589)
      - Residences: Penn. State Lodge, n.d. (Box 52, Folder 590)
      - Residences: Spenser House; William Penn Lodge, 1918,1924 (Box 52, Folder 591)
      - Residences: Wesleyan Mission House; Weyerhauser House, 1918, 1924 (Box 52, Folder 592)
      - Residences: Miscellaneous, 1911,1956 (Box 52, Folder 593)
      - Residences: Agricultural Residences, 1925-1926 (Box 65, Folder 718)
      - Residences: Blackstone Lodge (also known as the Chung residence), 1915 (Box 65, Folder 719)
      - Residences: Bradley House; Brownell House (see Mason Lodge #2, Folder 729), 1926-1927 (Box 65, Folder 720)
      - Residences: Coles Lodge, 1914-1924 (Box 65, Folder 721)
      - Residences: Double House #1, 1932 (Box 65, Folder 722)
      - Residences: Double House #2, #3, 1922,1930 (Box 65, Folder 723)
      - Residences: Gould Lodge; Holt House, 1916, 1920,1924 (Box 65, Folder 724)
      - Residences: Jackson Lodge (President's House), 1913-1925 (Box 65, Folder 725)
      - Residences: London Mission House, 1918-1932 (Box 65, Folder 726)
      - Residences: McCormick House #1, #2, 1913,1918 (Box 65, Folder 727)
      - Residences: Mason Lodge #1, 1924 (Box 65, Folder 728)
      - Residences: Mason Lodge #2 (also known as Brownell House), 1932 (Box 65, Folder 729)
      - Residences: Taam Lai Ting House (Alumni), 1925 (Box 65, Folder 730)
      - Sericulture Building, 1925-1931 (Box 53, Folder 594)
      - Swasey Hall, 1918,1920-32,1973 (Box 53, Folder 595)
      - Tea House Fruit Store, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 596)
      - Temporary Buildings, 1925-1930 (Box 53, Folder 597)
      - Views from Campus, 1925 (Box 53, Folder 598)
      - Views of College, 1906,1915-32,1973 (Box 53, Folder 599-600)
      - Water Works, 1931-1937 (Box 53, Folder 601)
      - Power Plant, 1926 (Box 53, Folder 601)
      - Street Cleaning Department, n.d. (Box 53, Folder 601)
      - Miscellaneous Buildings: Agricultural Hall; Medical College; Hospital; Grant Hall; Martin Hall; Meteorological Station, n.d. (Box OV4)
      - Tea House; The Wharf ;Athletic Field; Greenhouse; Water Tower; Dormitories; Blackstone House, n.d. (Box OV4)
      - Unidentified, n.d. (Box OV4)
      - Photos and maps used in Lingnan University history book (Box OV4)
    - South China scenes
      - Canton: Inauguration Day Scenes General Lei:Fuk Lam Dr. Sun, 1924 (Box 53, Folder 602)
      - Miscellaneous: Automobiles Bridges Trees Wall Mural Postcards (unidentified) Unidentified, 1933 (Box 53, Folder 603)
      - Miscellaneous City Scenes: Shameen and Canton City Flood Scene, Canton Honglok Honam Island, Canton Macao and Vicinity Whampoa, 1912-13,1929,1933 (Box 53, Folder 604)
      - Miscellaneous Public Places: Dutch Folly: Second Public Park Fati: Canton Flower Garden Lotus Pond (Box 53, Folder 605)
      - Miscellaneous: Pagodas and Towers Monuments Graves Statues, 1917,1926,1930 (Box 53, Folder 606)
      - Boat City at Canton Salt Junks on Pearl River Passenger Junks Refugee Boats Chinese Gunboats Citizen Soldiers Transport Lingnan Wharf, 1913,1924,1932 (Box 54, Folder 607)
      - Country Scenes Village Pictures, 1916 (Box 54, Folder 608)
      - Public Buildings and Places in Canton Private Residences Hackett Medical College Hospital, 1913,1938 (Box 54, Folder 609)
      - River Scenes (See also: OVERSIZE), 1922,1930,1933 (Box 54, Folder 610)
      - Roads, Streets in Canton and Shameen The Bund, Canton, 1908,1913 (Box 54, Folder 611)
      - Schools, Colleges (Miscellaneous) Chap Shun School,-Canton Old Educational Hall Chung Shan Memorial Library, 1912-1913 (Box 54, Folder 612)
      - Sun Yat-sen Memorial Building; Shops, Stores in Canton; Churches in Canton; Monasteries, 1931 (Box 54, Folder 613)
  - Campus Life
    - Agriculture
      - Agricultural Facilities and Exhibits, 1912,1919,1930 (Box 54, Folder 614)
      - Agricultural Projects Agricultural Institute for Refugee Children Kansas in Kwangtung Lingnan Boys' Farm Club College of Agriculture, 1917,1940 (Box 54, Folder 615)
      - Agricultural Projects, 1913-1916 (Box 55, Folder 616)
      - Animal Husbandry Cattle, goats, pigs, poultry, water buffalo; Dairying, 1913-1947 (Box 55, Folder 617-618)
    - Other campus activities
      - Arts Activities Drama, Music, 1925-1927,1941 (Box 55, Folder 619)
      - Athletics, 1907-1941 (Box 55, Folder 620)
      - Athletics Branch School Middle School Miscellaneous, 1924,1941 (Box 55, Folder 621)
      - Big Sisters, 1930 (Box 55, Folder 622)
      - Camera Club, 1937-1938 (Box 55, Folder 623)
      - Classroom Activities Domestic Sciences Laboratory, 1913-1932 (Box 56, Folder 624)
      - Classroom Activities, 1920-1940 (Box 56, Folder 625)
      - Classroom Activities Fish Pond Studies, 1924 (Box 56, Folder 626)
      - Classroom Activities Middle School, 1918-1930 (Box 56, Folder 627)
      - Constructing Fields, 1915,1918 (Box 56, Folder 628)
      - Crop Cultivation (A-L), 1913-1928 (Box 56, Folder 629)
      - Crop Cultivation (M-Z), 1913-1931 (Box 56, Folder 630)
      - Day Nursery and Orphanage, 1940 (Box 56, Folder 631)
      - Faculty Drama Productions, 1925,1929 (Box 56, Folder 632)
      - Library, 1922-1949 (Box 56, Folder 633)
      - Photo Album (unidentified: possibly from Dr. C.K. Edmunds), 1923-1924 (Box 57, Folder 634)
      - Photo Album, 1903 (Box 57, Folder 635)
      - Photo Album, 1910-1911 (Box 57, Folder 636)
      - School of Silk Industry, 1931 (Box 57, Folder 637)
      - Sericulture Activities Cocoon Market Silkworm Cultivation Wild Silkworms End Products (Box 57, Folder 638)
      - Sericultural Activities, 1926-1928,1931 (Box 57, Folder 639)
      - Arbor Day, 1917-1931 (Box 57, Folder 640)
      - Alumni Day Big Sisters Day Boys Day, 1925-1931 (Box 57, Folder 641)
      - Demonstration, 1925 Jun 23 (Box 57, Folder 642)
      - Fifteenth Anniversary Pageant, 1919 Nov 29 (Box 58, Folder 643)
      - Ground Breaking Ceremonies Building Openings, 1905-1969 (Box 58, Folder 644)
      - Inaugurations Memorial Services Special Receptions, 1913-1938 (Box 58, Folder 645)
      - Independence Day, 1924,1927 (Box 58, Folder 646)
      - Christmas Day Banquet, 1925
      - Thanksgiving Day, 1936,1938
      - Twenty-fifth Anniversary, 1929 Dec 6 (Box 58, Folder 647)
      - Women's Dormitory: Ground Breaking and Opening, 1933,1935 (Box 58, Folder 648)
      - Students - Military Organizations, 1914-1932 (Box 58, Folder 649)
      - Students - Women at Canton Christian College, 1920, n.d. (Box 58, Folder 650)
      - Swimming Pool, 1915-1916,n.d. (Box 58, Folder 651)
      - Miscellaneous, 1912-1937 (Box 58, Folder 652)
  - Individual and Group Portraits
    - Faculty
      - Entire Faculty and Students, 1908,1926,n.d. (Box 59, Folder 653)
      - Entire Faculty and Students: Christian Activities, 1917-1918,n.d. (Box 59, Folder 654)
      - Faculty and Staff, 1914-1923 (Box 59, Folder 655)
      - Faculty, 1924-1929 (Box 59, Folder 656)
      - Faculty, 1930-1937 (Box 59, Folder 657)
      - Chinese faculty: Chue Yau Kwong and wife Chung Wing Kwong, 1908-1931 (Box 59, Folder 658)
      - Chinese faculty: Lei Ying Lam, 1928 (Box 59, Folder 659)
      - Chinese faculty: Sz-to Wai, 1900,1926 (Box 59, Folder 660)
      - Western faculty: Baxter, A. and Family; Brownell, Henry and Family, 1908,1919,1926 (Box 59, Folder 661)
      - Western faculty: Cadbury, William and Family, 1916-1940 (Box 59, Folder 662)
      - Western faculty: Duncan, Kenneth and Family, 1911-1920 (Box 60, Folder 663)
      - Western faculty: Edmunds, Charles K., 1903,1916 (Box 60, Folder 664)
      - Western faculty: Howard, Harvey J., 1912-1928 (Box 60, Folder 665)
      - Western faculty: McClure, Floyd A., 1919 (Box 60, Folder 666)
      - Western faculty: MacDonald, W.E.; Morse, Dr. and Mrs., 1910,1928 (Box 60, Folder 667)
      - Western faculty: Wisner, Oscar Francis and Family, 1898,1928-1929 (Box 60, Folder 668)
      - Western faculty: Woods, Andrew H. and Family, 1914 (Box 60, Folder 669)
      - Western faculty: Miscellaneous (A-Q), 1903-1935 (Box 60, Folder 670)